Hello, I'm Nachiko and Nanako Ogawa, the minty-greenies from Candy Tune!
Hi, we're Nachiko and Nanako Ogawa.
I'm kind of smiling.
I'm kind of smiling. All the time.
I'm smiling sometimes. I don't know...
Are you cheerful? I'm curious. It's hard for me to focus on one thing.
I'm good at everything I do.
I've heard a lot about Linomar and Kiri, but before I met them, I thought Linomar and Kiri would never get along.
They thought I was like a girl on Instagram, but once I got to know them better than I thought I would...
I've been told on social media that I'm going to start an idol group belonging to the Asobi System, and when I got responses from everyone, they all said, "Oh, you're so cute!
I'm going to be a member of the idol group from the Asobi system.
I've been doing this for about a month or two now, and the time I've spent doing it is slowly starting to show.
When I was little, I was very shy,
I didn't want to go to school or kindergarten anymore,
There were times when I clung to my desk and wouldn't go.
Shy? Shy? I am.
Now I feel like an outsider.
I'm a lesbian.
I'm not particularly expressive,
I don't have a lot of facial expressions,
I want to make eye contact with my fans.
I want to make eye contact with every single person, even if they are not my fans.
I want to make eye contact with as many people as possible at one show, even if they are not my fans.
But I laugh a lot.
When I laugh, I lose eye contact.
They may not even know that I'm making eye contact with them.
I'm like, "I'm looking at you.
I was a figure skater until I was in the third grade of junior high school.
When it came time for the entrance examinations
I decided to concentrate on my studies, so I took a short break from figure skating to concentrate on my exams.
I took a break from figure skating for a while to concentrate on studying for the entrance examinations.
I was tired after 9 years of figure skating,
I guess I was so exhausted after 9 years of skating, that I had to take a break from skating,
I was not able to study at all during the period when I had to concentrate on studying for the entrance examinations,
In the end, I lost both of them between junior high school and high school.
I had to quit figure skating as well,
I also failed to get into the high school I wanted to go to.
I lost both of them, and I was dragging it out for about 2 years, that's when I was the sickest.
I was rebelling against my parents, and I was falling apart.
I don't think there are many groups where the members are open to the public for months before their debut and communicate with their fans through sns.
That's why we want to be a group with passion so that people won't think we're just cute.
I have been figure skating since I was 6 years old, so figure skating has been my life.
I've been dancing to music in cute costumes since I was a little girl.
and performing in front of the audience.
I loved it so much.
I thought that my becoming an idol
It was not by chance that I became an idol, but by necessity.
In fact, after I lost figure skating, which was my life
I overcame my life and became an idol.
Idols are the ones who gave me a second life.
I hope that someone will see me and have a dream like that.
I hope I can be the kind of person who can help people find their place in the world.
I really hope that I can be someone who can find their own place in the world.
Candy Tune is the future for me.
Yay!
What? You make me feel light.
It's the future!
You.